CHAIM TEITELBAUM - DATA ANALYST/SCIENTIST

Brooklyn, NY. 11218

Phone: 929/420-2138 | Email: mailto:palmartdesign@yahoo.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/palmartdesign/

GitHub: https://github.com/ChaimTeitelbaum Portfolio: https://github.com/ChaimTeitelbaum

SUMMARY

Data Analyst with a background in logistics management, using technical abilities in data analysis and data mining to provide in-depth and insightful solutions to complex problems. Recognized for excellent communication abilities in multiple languages, including client relationship development. An accomplished artist, bringing a creative-thought process from experience in painting, drawing, graphic design and architecture.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Skills:	Experience:
Python	 Visual Artist/Painter.
JavaScript	 Drawing & Illustrator.
SQL	o Graphic Design.
Matplotlib	 Architectural blueprints.
Tableau	o Visual Effects
Data Mining	 Years Logistic management
Data Analysis	Soft skills:
Communication:	o time management
 Great written and oral communicati 	on o innovative
skills.	o conflict resolution
 Multilingual. 	

PROJECTS

Project Name: ETL Project: | https://github.com/ChaimTeitelbaum/ETL_project

Link to Project Description:

https://github.com/ChaimTeitelbaum/ETL_project/blob/master/Description%20of%20project%20steps

- Project summary: Analyze NYPD hate crime records
- Responsibilities in the project were: parts of data transformation / cleaning and the Loading
- Tools / lang. used: Jupyter Notebook. Python. Pandas. SQLAlchemy. PostgreSQL.

Project Name: ETL Project: | https://github.com/ChaimTeitelbaum/Project2-fullstack

Link to Deployed Project: https://github.com/ChaimTeitelbaum/ETL project/blob/master/Description

- Project summary: Stock symbol research and dashboard with few gages
- Responsibilities in the project were: parts of data extraction cleaning and the Loading
- Tools / lang. used: HTML/CSS/Flask/D3 Jupyter Notebook. Python. Pandas. SQLAlchemy.

Project Name: ML Project: | https://github.com/ChaimTeitelbaum/Project 3

Link to Deployed Project: | https://github.com/ChaimTeitelbaum/Project 3

- Project summary: Song recognition like Shazam
 Responsibilities: Python, figure out the best way to test and train the machine
- Tools / lang. used: HTML/CSS/Flask/JS Jupyter Notebook. Python. Pandas. SQLite

EXPERIENCE

1996 – 2005: Artist / Graphic Design 2005 – 2013: Artist oil on canvas / Murals 2013 – 2015: Logistics 2015 – Current: Logistic coordinator at Sam Maintenance Inc. Brooklyn, NY Responsibilities:

- Communicate with the Clients assure faster service and mostly safety of the operations.
- Using multi-linguistic skills to communicate in several languages with clients

Key Accomplishments:

• Client relationship great and Company has prospered and had greater success due to the achievements.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: Columbia University, Brooklyn, NY

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Python, JavaScript, jQuery, Matplotlib, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Degree: Bootcamp Certificate: Columbia University, Brooklyn, NY